[music]
Yesterday in Austin, people climbed into
Teslas with no steering wheels, no
pedals, and nobody in the driver's seat.
After years of promises, the Cyber Cab
is finally real. But if you were hoping
that yesterday's launch was going to
explain exactly how this is going to
scale, you're probably disappointed.
There was no Elon, no live stream, and
no real production ramp update, no new
city timelines, and still no final
pricing. Although you can fill out a
form and let Tesla know that you're
interested in buying your own fleet. Uh,
people who actually rode in the Cyber
Cabs genuinely seemed impressed. There
was insane leg room and recline and
huge, huge screen and a smooth ride. One
person called it the nicest $25,000 car
you've ever seen in your life. And
starting tonight at 5:00 p.m., cyber cab
rides are going to be open to the
public. So, yes, there's still a lot
that Tesla hasn't told us, but something
changed yesterday. Robo taxi is no
longer just an Elon Musk promise. People
are riding in it and now we get to
figure out exactly what that is worth.
Today on Dumb Money, Tesla's robo taxi
is finally real. Now what happens to
Tesla's stock? [music] This is Dumb
Money Live.
>> Hey there, Dave here along with Chris
and Jordan. We are Dumb Money. Welcome
to Dumb Money Live. If you're willing to
get into a car with no steering wheel,
no pedals, uh you should you should
definitely have no problem finding the
like button and just smashing the heck
out of it. Chris Jordan, uh it has been
so long since we've done one of these.
We're we're still working out the
technical uh technical issues behind the
scenes, but thanks for thanks for
finally uh being with us on our podcast,
Chris, instead of your world tour of
other people's podcasts.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, I'm just promoting dumb money
everywhere I go.
>> It's great. It's great. So, anyway,
yesterday Tesla um basically gave us
something we've been waiting for uh
years to see, but none of the numbers
that that actually moved the stock. So,
I don't know exactly where to start. The
Dumb Money AI robot created this
eightpage uh analyst report for us. So,
I've got all of my notes firmly uh
situated here.
Where do we tell you where to start,
Dave? Uh, I think I'm going to piss off
some Tesla people on this call, and I
hate doing that, but I I got to speak
the truth. Um, before I do that, I want
to say one thing really positive about
Tesla.
>> Uh, my buddy, our buddy, longterm buddy
Patrick, you know, he he had a Model Y,
which I was like, whatever.
>> He got the new Model Y, which I hadn't
been inside of until yesterday. I had
lunch with Patrick. If you were in town,
you would have been with us, Dave, at
Sammy's.
>> Barbecue Sammy.
>> Best one of the best barbecue in the
city. Uh,
>> I know, Patrick. I didn't get a phone
call.
>> I You're just also,
>> you know, I'm on Sammies. You know,
>> I'm sorry, dude. Nissan, you're in.
You're in.
>> You're in. Let me just say something.
Like, legit, I was so stunned by how
beautiful the interior of the new Model
Y is. Honestly, it was flawless. It was,
you know, how like Teslas are a little
hard. They feel like a little too
futuristic. They don't feel comfortable.
They don't feel soft. They just don't
>> The original ones in that the stark
white interiors. It It felt like the
future, but almost not in a good way.
>> I They fixed every problem with this new
Model Y. If you guys have not been in
the new Model Y, and I know I'm so late
to comment on this, like I should have
been people that follow Tesla probably
knew about this forever ago, but the
interior of that Model Y is a work of
art. It is warm. It's soft. The
materials, the the sun, every single
piece of that interior is gorgeous. I
just a work of art. I was so floored by
it because, you know, that's not my type
of car, Dave. I drive it, you know.
>> I really like the way the exterior
looks. Although, I wish for their SUV
light type vehicle, they would make it
look more like an SUV and less like a
sedan. But I So, it's going to be
Megan's next car for sure. Um, and and
probably as soon as we get back to
Texas, I'll be buying that.
>> You're going to get the X. I'm just I
would wait and get the new Genesis. Your
health deserves more.
>> Wait, get the
>> the new Genesis that's coming out. The
new Genesis SUV. Uh, easy.
>> Oh, with the with the the doors that
open like this. Yeah, that that looks
pretty insane. But no, I'm not going to
buy it. I'm not going to buy that.
>> How about a Honda?
>> Genesis.
>> A Hyundai.
>> And it's it's Genesis
highend Hyundai
>> of their higherend unit.
>> I'm not ripping. I love Hyundai. I as a
I
>> But it's a Genesis. But yeah, it's under
the Hyundai uh corporation. It actually
looks crazy and
>> it looks awesome
>> as far as like a car that's actually
slated for production and not just a
concept car. It's like the craziest
thing I've seen, but it doesn't have
full self-drive, which is the whole
thing about Tesla, which is my next car
is going to be a Tesla 100% because I
just don't like driving. And the idea of
a cyber cab that will drive me around or
my own car that will drive me around and
go park itself drop me off at the
airport and go home and and park itself
in the garage. That is the future.
>> I don't trust a LAR self-driving system.
So I'm a past.
>> Oh, you're
>> you're a LAR man, aren't you?
>> I didn't even realize how big of a man
he was. You're you're
>> He's driving around. He's He can't wait
to get in his zuks.
[laughter]
>> Jordan, I I don't necessarily disagree
with you, though. Um, but yeah, the tech
dude, that Model Y was [\h__\h] crazy
nice, man. Good props.
>> My brother-in-law's got one. I rode it.
It's great. They look awesome.
>> I I feel like I feel like Elon does not
have a nuance sense. He has no taste
when it comes to anything beyond raw
technology.
Like in ter in terms of like actual
human taste, I just don't think he has
it. But someone on his team over him.
>> Yeah.
>> And you know what? You know what I think
happened? I think that Elon is so
focused on other things the last 18 24
months that his team actually got to
make some decisions without him being
overly involved. And whoever is running
at least on the interior of that car is
insane. But let's talk about the cyber
>> the cyber
>> cab
>> cab because this thing guys by the way
there's so much misinformation out
there. Like there's just people the
stock chart of the last two days makes
so much sense to me. This is exactly
what I would think would happen because
the hype going into that event and on
the surface what Tesla was putting out
was phenomenal. But as soon as you start
peeling off the layers of truth and
actually assessing the viability, the
timelines, the economics, and how all of
this is actually going to play out, by
the way, potentially very good, but the
timelines
and at the valuation level,
>> this entire
FSD robo taxi thing is a very good to
great thing for Tesla which is already
baked into the price. Period. End of
story. All of it. Like all of it is
baked into Tesla's price right now
because even
>> is it baked in at the best case
scenario, the mid-range scenario or like
it barely barely ever took off, right?
Um because it's a small so like you
still got a small sample of cars that
are being put into this. By the way, the
only way that they can even do this is
Texas because of the regulations that
are in California. They can't do a
self-driving uh test like this or I mean
a full autonomous taxi in California
right now.
>> Jordan, forget about a small sampling of
cars. If they were to ramp this up to a
million, okay, a million site robo cabs
or whatever.
>> Well, they haven't made enough cars to
do that.
>> Well, even at that, if you look at the
economics, which are kind of debatable,
it's very early. There's a lot of
factors and you know a lot of more
questions and answers but you're looking
at like tens of billions of profit
annually at like a million of these
things. And do you know how difficult
it's going to be to get a million of
these things with all the different
regulatory issues state by state by
state? We are looking at so far down the
road. So you're telling me that once you
get a million of them, realistically
we're looking at tens of billions. Throw
on a PE cuz at that point it's a pretty
mature business. It's not going to be a
wild PE. We're looking at a fraction of
Tesla's valuation already today. Yeah.
>> So like it's very hard to get and I've
been saying this for a long time. Elon
knows this by the way. Elon has said
this. The entirety of Tesla is optimist.
We're not going to talk about optimist
right this second.
>> Yes. But Optimus is everything. It's
everything.
>> We need We do need to to talk about it a
little bit because how much of Optimus
is priced in and Elon has said that
Optimus will be 80% of Tesla in the
future. So does cyber cab does robo taxi
really matter and how much? Because
you're talking a million cars or AI,
>> right? It's just a it's just a portion.
>> Okay, I'll tell you. calculated that 2
million cyber cabs could do a 105
billion of annual bookings and at a 30%
operating margin that's $31 billion
uh
>> so that doesn't it's it's not it's not
like
>> critical
>> it guys it's it's actually nothing when
you look at the valuation of Tesla it's
so all of the future potential
theoretical
economic benefit from robo
Cab is fully baked in to Tesla stock
right now. So there's essentially zero
upside. Zero. Okay. There's one thing
that makes Robo Cab extremely important.
Right. And there's one thing only. The
only thing that matters. Do I am I
saying it right? Robo. Before you go
there. Before you go there.
>> Robo taxi.
>> Robo taxi. See why? All right. Take all
that back.
>> There's cyber cab which is the name of
the gold car
>> and then robo taxi which is the service.
Okay. So, both cyber cab, robo taxi,
whatever. There's only there's only one
thing that matters,
>> but don't reveal it yet.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> I need you to I need you to repost this
episode on X so that people can actually
hear this most important thing.
>> Oh my god.
>> Dude, this is the problem. When we we
literally don't we haven't
>> We do an episode every other month now.
We're we're really really slackers.
>> Oh my Oh, here we go. Okay, dude. I'm
sorry. Now it's it's it's reposted. All
right.
>> Okay. What is the one thing that matters
>> for everybody that is hopefully popping
on X right now? We're talking about
[snorts] Cyber
Cab and Robo Taxi. Okay. The only thing
that matters because the entirety of the
success of that program is baked into
Tesla stock right now. But there's one
thing that's not baked in and that is if
Tesla can actually execute on robo taxi,
okay, in a very big way, the numbers are
not going to really matter that much
relative to the valuation of Tesla, but
it's going to serve as a proof point
that Tesla is more likely than not to
pull off
Optimus, which is rough. roughly 100 to
a thousand times the size of uh robo
taxi. Okay, so 100 to a thousand times
the size. So if Tesla fails at this,
people are going to be less confident in
their ability to pull off something that
is actually more difficult, which is
Optimus, the robot. But if they succeed
and they execute and they show that they
actually have their crap together after
the last few years of mis expectations
and being kind of all over the place and
Elon being all over the place now will
start to develop a confidence that these
guys can be a top one two company
globally in robotics generalized
robotics and that is what gets you the
theoretical 10 trillion 1520 trillion
valuation at some point in the future.
That's what could potentially excite
institutional and retail investors, even
those guys that are are informed and are
actually basing Tesla's market cap on
something real because that's actually
not just a theoretical, it's very real
if they execute. So that's what we saw
yesterday. Yeah. What we saw yesterday
basically proves that in from an
engineering standpoint and from a like
being able to go from concept to a
product that you can actually get in and
ride around in Tesla can do that. Check.
And they'll probably be able to build a
robot that that has capacity to scale.
But turning that into a subscription
business, turning that into a
a number that actually helps their stock
price, we need we need Tesla to prove
that with I think that CyberCap is a
good example of of a technology that has
a business model kind of, but they
haven't been able to do it yet.
>> I mean, there's just still so many
questions uh with robo taxi, right? like
regulatory even where they're able to do
this like they still have regulatory
humps to get through. There's requests
that have to be
>> there's there's the audit that the
transportation safety board is is doing.
There's the uh Tesla has this this
concept that they can bypass that
because this car doesn't have controls.
So, some of the safety features that are
in most normal cars or all normal cars
required to be there, uh, they get an
exemption from that and, uh, you know,
that's that's a big unknown for
>> Well, they're just not even leading the
market here, right? I mean, Whimo is the
obvious market leader. They're way ahead
of
>> but I think that Whimo Whimo being ahead
and actually having more cars on the
road all is is a positive for Tesla
because they're going they're kind of
having to deal with the exact same
regulatory issues. They have a way more
expensive and hard to produce vehicle
>> in a little bit different way. There's
different engineering behind it. So
it's, you know, it's a different it's a
different animal, right? That it's
different.
But Jordan, the entire thesis around
robo taxi is that at some point, it
doesn't matter how far ahead Whimo and
the other guys are, that at some point
the cost efficiencies of robo taxi will
be so meaningfully
superior to Whimo that it will be almost
an impossibility for companies like
Whimo to compete. Now, I'm not saying
that's correct because there's still a
lot of questions around that. There's a
lot of questions.
>> Are you just saying because the car is
more stripped down, right? So, it's
easier to it's it's less expensive to
put each individual
>> nice. I think I think it's about more
than that. I think yes the strip down
nature of the car uh you know the the
the lack of LAR the l and then also just
the mass manufacturing expertise at
scale of Tesla also uh the fact that
they are going to have a program that is
going to you know share the cost of that
with fleet management companies there's
just a really there are a lot of
benefits if they can execute and I think
that all those things combined Jordan I
think are going to not create the
greatest economic model for Tesla, but
what it will do is destroy the economic
model of Tesla competitors that are
coming in at a way higher cost. So, I
don't think this is like as insanely
great of a business as we all once
thought it would be for Tesla, but I do
think it could theoretically be crushing
for companies like Whimo. And then also,
I want to talk about this. This is
>> also like Uber and Lift, right?
>> Yeah. I think I I think this is where
the trade gets really interesting. If if
I when I looked at this, the one thing
that stuck with me is shorting Uber. And
I know it's a controversial take,
but I just do not see how Uber survives
with the existing economics that they've
been enjoying because the economics are
going to get shattered no matter how you
look at this. Even if Uber does their
own thing in driverless, it really
doesn't matter because if Tesla succeeds
with with, you know, robo taxi, they it
just shatters the economics for everyone
else. And I I I don't it just seems like
the riskreward here is in your favor
long term of shorting Uber. Now, the
timeline, that's a whole different
story.
>> Yeah, the timeline's tough, right? Um
Uber Eats is a little tougher to disrupt
with this model. Um,
>> yeah. I I think that like short straight
up shorting Uber is dangerous. I think
if if you could find a financial way to
like
play the distance between Tesla and
Uber, that would be more interesting.
But like Uber has other stuff. Uber is
not just self-driving. Uber is a
logistics company.
Um,
yeah. I I I I don't know. I mean, people
would say that the, you know, the mode
on Uber is is the rider, not the driver,
right? Um,
you know, and then people say that they
die when the robo taxi companies no
longer need all of that demand. So like
the big question is can a company like
Tesla circumvent the existing
demand that only falls under Uber today
because of habit and because of all the
years that Uber has you know developed
that customer relationship which by the
way I would say is a terrible customer
relationship. I hate Uber. Uber has had
years and years to perfect that
experience. And the Uber experience has
done nothing but gotten worse. I see
more cars that are filthy. I And the
worst is the odor. It's the worst damn
smelling experience. And by the way,
this is so easily fixable. Do you know
how cheap it would be for Uber to say,
"If you want to be an Uber, you must put
this filtration system, this this
Christmas tree on your dash to make it
not smell so freaking bad. put the
Christmas tree on your dash. I hate
those even worse that I just want a
neutral scent. I don't want the little
trees. I I literally cannot handle that.
You know how Uber has the the the
version where you say, "Yes, I want a
quiet ride and I want it to be cool."
They need to have a want it to be
odorless.
>> And that is a sensory issue that I
personally have that I cannot stand. And
when a car pulls up with a better
experience, I I don't use Uber. I only
use lift and I have nothing but good
experience.
>> But Jordan, you also live in the country
basically.
>> No, I just got back from Manhattan and I
took Lift all around Manhattan and I had
no problems.
>> Well, you got you you got lucky.
>> No, I have like 10 different lift rides
and they were all fantastic. Friendly
people, five stars all the way. They
were all
>> By the way, that's great. But what tells
what it still is like a roll of the dice
in my opinion. And my issue is this. If
Uber is incapable of solving the most
easily solvable problem, which is making
sure that your drivers aren't high and
that the cars don't smell like DO, then
that management team is incapable of
existing in a world of driverless cars.
Okay? The whole bearish outcome isn't
that Uber loses every single ride. It's
that they keep the rides, okay? some of
them, but they're financing the cars and
they're losing all of the margin. And by
the way, their customer base doesn't
really care about them because nobody
wants to be in a smelly car driven by a
guy that's high. Like it's just not safe
and it's disgusting and it's like one
out of every three rides right now for
me.
>> Um, are you are you Uber X or do you get
like the upgrade? You get the
>> Dude, I am
>> the Lux or whatever.
>> No, I'll do a comfort, you know? I'll do
an Uber comfort. Yeah,
>> I I'll but I don't really do a black
kind. Come on now.
>> I do I do like the lip the upgraded one
the just one step up and I've got no
problem. I never
>> not a step up. That's the problem. You
get sometimes you get lucky. Sometimes
you don't get lucky. But
>> I get real lucky then because I have no
issues on
>> you get you get you get guaranteed a
newer vehicle but you don't get
guaranteed a better driver or a better
overall experience.
>> Do you know what I want? I want to pay a
little extra for a vehicle that doesn't
smell bad. Why don't they have a
>> I would pay for the sensory experience
vehicle. Absolutely. Okay. I think this
would be a fun game. I in our notes I
saw that rumor and claim scorecard and
it just seemed like a perfect
opportunity for us to debunk some of the
rumors to confirm some of the the
statements that have been out there. So,
let's just go through this list. I will
I will read the claim and then I want
you to tell me what you think. So the
claim is CyberCAB is now operating
publicly.
>> What does that mean?
>> Trueish
>> public cybercab will be public as of
5:00 pm tonight. You'll be able to get
in a cyber cab in Austin, Texas
>> within a within a like geofenced area.
>> Yes. And also not guaranteed the actual
the actual like the cool one that
everyone
>> you may not get the gold one. You may
get a model.
>> They don't guarantee that you're going
to get one of those. Well, there's not
>> there's only 45 in Austin, right? And
there's like 500 normal ones. So like
you have a one in 10 chance.
>> Yeah.
>> Of getting it.
>> And if you need extra space, you can't
use it anyways. You can only do two
people.
>> It's a two person two. It's a two seat.
>> Two person max.
>> If you have four people, you're going to
need the model there. But
>> yeah.
>> Okay. Next claim is Tesla has a thousand
cyber cabs on the road.
>> No,
>> Jordan.
>> What? No. No way.
>> It is It is false. It is misleading. The
uh the transportation audit population
of a thousand. Uh but but it's actually
Texas has 45 registered cyber cabs. So
it's they're not the same thing.
>> By the way, [laughter] they have a
thousand possible
I I do think that half of all the cyber
cabs are in Austin and Dallas, Texas
because like
>> they're all over Dallas. They were even
in Dallas the last time I was there.
>> What do you guys think about the the
gold? I think it's disgusting. I I think
it's
>> the gold.
>> I think it photographs better than it
looks.
>> You think it's awesome?
>> I don't have a problem with I think it
looks great.
>> Okay. But have you seen them in the
wild? Because they look horrible when
they get dirty, Jordan. And when I say
horrible
>> Yeah, I know. I can see that.
I had gold Tahoe ones and it always look
terrible. Dude,
>> I think I think they look great in the
promotional videos, but in person they
just look a little bit
>> not the same vibrant vibrant gold.
>> When I see them in the wild, these uh
cyber c what what do they call? I keep
getting the name.
>> Cyber cab.
>> Yeah. When I see them in the wild, these
cyber cabs look like a really crappy car
at a Mad Max covered in dirt. The
problem is what color is the best color
for Dinge? And I feel like gold might be
it, right?
>> Actually, I think here's what gold has
going for it. It kind of when you see
them in mass,
>> it kind of reminds you of the New York
City yellow cabs. So, it's like a
futuristic take on a yellow cab. And
because it is a cyber cab,
>> I kind of think the gold works. I'm not
all upset about the gold being the
color.
>> Yeah,
>> I don't like it. I I I don't like it. We
We'll see what happens. I do get that
they're trying to do something radically
different that doesn't make any sense at
first, but then over time you're like,
that was genius. Kind of like the yellow
cab, Dave. That does make sense.
>> You would have never chosen yellow in
and if you were starting over from
scratch building taxis in Manhattan and
you wouldn't have picked yellow, right?
>> But now it's iconic on green.
>> I I think they litter the neighborhood
with ugliness. They're they're nasty.
And by the way, like I know the Whimos
are kind of nasty, but like with all the
stuff like but but I almost prefer to
see a Whimo zooming around in that nasty
dirty gold.
>> I can't stand the the Whimos the Whimo
in our neighborhood, Chris.
>> And the cars themselves, like the the
cyber cabs, they're streamlined. Like
they look sleek. I I think it's a good
look.
>> I think it's a good look. I I think that
the the Whimos in our neighborhood that
just always are parking themselves
because they don't have any demand, they
look they look I I'm not a fan of them.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, next claim and you you might
be seeing a lot more of these gold
things driving around the neighborhood.
The claim is the factory can make
125,000 of these per year. True or
false?
True.
capacity doesn't mean they're going to
do that though, right?
>> That's right.
>> Okay.
>> Wait, what was the what was the
question?
>> Whe whether or not they So, the claim is
they can do $125,000
$125,000
vehicles per year uh in the cyber cab
factory. And it's partially true. That
is their maximum capacity. That's not
where they are today.
>> Yeah, I'm sure they can. They're not
doing it. I think this is one of the
things that the Tesla fanboys often run
away with. Every time they announce
their manufacturing capacity, people
just assume they're doing like I see
this with the robots all the time.
People like, oh, they they're going to
be doing a million and a half up. I'm
like, dude, no. Maybe theoretically in
the future. Trust me, there are no plans
to be making that many robots. They do
not have a a a hardware scalable
platform that would work anywhere right
now. So like what's the point of making
any beyond what you need to train with?
So there so many misconceptions between
those two things. I'm glad you said
that.
>> You can't take the maximum possible
output from the factory and multiply it
by the best case scenario for like
oper, you know, dollar per mile and
expect that to be accurate.
>> Yeah. Also Dave like at that capacity it
might end up actually being more cost. I
mean they might have to you know employ
too many people at higher wages. Who
knows? So like the optimal manufacturing
capacity could be half that.
>> Yeah. And what the next claim is that
rides are going to cost 20 cents per
mile. What do you or false on that?
false.
>> I'm I'm going to assume like everything
else when it comes to cost and Tesla,
it's just someone's estimate that no one
really knows anything about. More
question.
>> It's a madeup number and and that is the
answer. It is unsupported as a current
fair, but 20 cents per mile is their
aspirational goal number. That's what
they that's where they want to get.
>> Okay. Sure. So also on price cyber
>> numbers like that is it like it's so
dependent on where you are
geographically because like a mile in
Manhattan is totally different than a
mile you know in you know Missouri
somewhere right?
>> Yeah I think when it comes to anything
like costwise
it's probably appropriate out of Tesla
to add 50%. anything when it comes to
time wise, three to five times the
amount of time that they say it's
[laughter] going to take, maybe 10 times
the amount of time.
>> The current claim is that cyber cabs
will cost less than $30,000.
You're saying that that's off by 50%.
>> Probably
up to up to 50%. So like I don't know it
I think it's probably off to some
extent.
>> Yeah. I mean, they might end up it might
being like one of those things where
>> they do have a lot less components than
them, right? So, like the most expensive
part is the battery. The battery is
probably worth about 12 grand and then,
you know, the rest of the car, but it
doesn't even have a steering wheel,
right? So,
>> it doesn't have a steering wheel. It the
batteries are specialized uh for this
vehicle. Uh the the the engine, the
motor is uh specialized. They're they're
using um different materials for this.
They're using no uh what are the rare
earth metals at all for for the uh
motor.
>> So Dave, here's what I think. Here's
what I think they'll end up doing. When
was that price first announced? What
year was that first floated?
>> I have no idea.
>> Okay, let's just say it was 2020. I
don't know if
>> I feel like he's been saying this is
going to be a $25,000 car for years.
>> Okay. I I I think they're going to come
out and say that they were able to do it
inflation adjusted from when they first
made that prediction and it's like
37,000. [laughter]
But
>> that takes care of the number right
there because and and that was the
target. Um but there they have no
confirmation on price or delivery
schedule. Nothing uh real in that
regard.
>> Totally. Yeah. Um, so the the next claim
is that cyber cabs will be sold to
individuals and businesses right now.
>> Uh, they they can't sell anything right
now, but I mean they're probably
starting the process, I would assume,
but there's nothing being sold. There's
nothing being sold.
>> At this point, they're just taking uh
interest in potentially owning a fleet.
>> Yeah.
>> Which Yeah.
>> is crazy. And actually the kind of the
more interesting part of their business
model, they get money upfront for
manufacturing a vehicle. They get the
markup on on the manufacturing and then
don't have to operate the vehicle and
just get to take a uh pure revenue off
the top of the rides.
>> Okay. So, somebody just made a comment.
Jesse Cumberledge just said, "Remember,
no one has actually turned a profit with
the robo taxi network yet." I mean,
yeah, it's early, but also I think the
comment's right. Do wouldn't Tesla just
want to be in the business if they
wanted to be in that business instead of
making fleets and selling them off to
people? I It just seems like a bad
>> I think they're they're in the business
in just the right way. I think that that
it's it's the most
>> I I would think that if Uber could
figure out a way to do it, they would do
it.
>> Uber for your product. Like, is that the
>> Jordan? I'll tell you why. I'll tell you
why. Okay. Um here's why. one, I don't
think Elon cares that much uh about the
ultimate end margin of this unit because
he knows that it will be a very tiny
piece of Tesla over time. I think he
cares more about executing and scaling
quickly. So, it's going to take so long
to get all this regulatory approved. By
the time it's approved, the quickest way
to scale is the same way that Amazon
scaled with third party delivery driver.
The quickest way to scale this thing
would be to just offer them through Lift
and Uber, right? Um
>> well well well Jordan, but but no, he
does not he want he does not want to
concentrate power with one or two
competing companies. He would much
rather less have he'd much rather have
thousands and thousands of small to
medium-siz fleet management companies
pop up. This has been the Tesla way,
right? And I think the biggest thing
Tesla has going for it is there is
tremendous demand both from individuals
and small to medium business operators
that are dying to get in this space.
They've been thinking about it for
years. This is a cash flow business.
They would all love to buy 20 or 40 or
50 robo taxis and operate them as a
small business and make a few
hundred,000 a year. That's a really cool
thing for a lot of people to want to do.
I just think from a passion standpoint,
there's so many people passionate about
this and Tesla, he will he has massive
demand. Massive. And Jordan, here's the
thing. He can get better economics from
a fragmented market of fleet management
companies than he could negotiating with
Uber or Lyft. Okay. So,
>> why not just roll out your own why not
just operate them yourself, right?
>> Because he he he can he doesn't have to
pay for it. First of all, it's other
people's money.
point, right?
>> He gets to operate the factories and
then collect money upfront while someone
else is financing the actual cost of
operations and he's getting dollars per
mile too.
>> But you Jordan, you get to outsource
all of the local knowledge, the
headaches because remember each of these
you're going to have to be connecting
them to power clean. By the way,
cleaning clean. Do you think Tesla wants
to be over cleaning a million cars every
three days, right?
>> When if you think about just cleaning,
>> segment it to people that own like 30 to
100 and they're responsible for those
100 vehicles and they can deal
>> it's kind of like Amazon outsourcing
their delivery to small businesses in
regional markets uh that that operate
their fleet of delivery cars.
Amazon does have some delivery that they
do themselves, but they've outsourced
and you get your Amazon vest and you get
to go be an Amazon.
>> Do you know that Mandami is trying to uh
uh cancel that in Manhattan and make
Amazon employ all those employees? Do
you know have any idea how high
>> delivery costs will go up if they
actually win and force Amazon to do
that?
>> Goodbye free delivery in Manhattan.
Well, it's not to mention how many small
business owners are going to go out of
business that operate all those tiny
delivery fleet management companies all
over Manhattan. I'm just I'm not even
going to get into it. It pisses me off
so much quite honestly. But I love the
model for Robo. I think that's actually
the smartest part of this model.
>> Just sell them. Let people create fleets
and
>> Yeah. Yeah. and you just just let them
deal with all the headaches cuz think
about
>> the only thing that Tesla loses there is
the control over the experience but they
can control most of it with software and
hardware. You know it how clean is the
vehicle? Are you going to get the smelly
the smelly uh cyber cabs? You you lose
control over that.
>> I honestly am boggled over Uber's
inability to control the experience. It
doesn't seem that hard to me. I don't
know, man. like how hard can it possibly
>> I mean there's a feedback system for all
this stuff right and that's so like
whenever I get out of the lip it asks me
it doesn't just say do you want to give
them five stars it says you know was the
experience good or bad right and then
what was good about it and I can say it
was a clean car I can say it was a good
driver I can say you know all these
different things right and so get that
feedback as long as you're then
reinccorporating it into
>> yeah they're doing nothing with the
feedback at least in my experience
Uber's experience the the Uber
experience has gotten so bad and I
report every car that smells. But
>> prevent smelly cars from coming to me.
>> If I was a consultant for Uber, I could
>> I could fix this problem overnight.
First of all, the feedback system needs
to be more oneclick for known problems
like odor. So, it's literally ask you
smell good or bad, hit every single
>> That's what I'm saying is that Lyft
already does that. Lift Lift does those
things, right? It lets you pick all
those different categories.
>> Well, I'll start I'll start using Lyft.
I'll see how
>> also use the carrot and the stick. I
would give the driver a range of cut. So
if they're making I don't know 60 to 70%
they can get the higher end of that
range if they address this problem or if
they at the higher you know higher end
of this of this scale in terms of the
things that are critical at that moment
in time which might be odor. So you go
all in on odor for six months and you
fix that problem.
This is not that difficult. I'm not
going to solve it but I could. I could
if they hired me.
>> It's too bad you're not you're not
working for any of [clears throat] these
companies. [laughter]
>> Oh, I need be done in a quarter.
>> All right. What's What's next, Dave?
>> Are we still doing this? I I I think we
we any good ones went off the rails with
this game.
>> All right. All right.
>> But if if you want to keep going, I can
I can give you some more.
>> I like it. I like it. What do you got?
>> All right. So, uh manual control cyber
cabs are coming for consumers. You'll be
able to buy one with the steering wheel
and pedals.
>> No, that's not the plan.
>> I don't It's a rumor.
>> It's a claim.
>> It is a rumor.
>> Uh the the the current status of that is
completely unconfirmed. They're saying
that Teslas have been seen with the
steering wheels and pedals obviously
because that's how they're they're, you
know, driving around and proving the
concept in these cities, but it's uh not
a retail product announcement. There's
there's a lot of people saying that, oh,
this is people people thought
yesterday's event was going to be so
many things from like unveiling of uh
Optimus 3 to like unveiling a a opening
an order form where you could just buy
the car tomorrow.
None of those things are happening.
>> We we should we should talk about that
because this is this has been bugging me
[clears throat] so much lately. Uh but
by the way, this is why that stock chart
the last day on Tesla perfectly perfect
perfectly reflects reality. Tremendous
hype on the surface level. Cool. As soon
as you start peeling the layers off, you
realize that there are 10x more
questions and answers and the timelines
are all over the place. and the stock
completely got destroyed and came back
down to where it was before the event.
Deservedly so. Deservedly so. Um, now
>> I think there's there's always a
communication problem with Tesla. I
think if Tesla had set expectations that
this was not a live stream event. This
is just a an employee party where we're
inviting some of the uh the the friendly
media, the the influencers, the
YouTubers. Uh we're we're just gonna
we're going to show you what we what we
have. We're going to let you ride in the
cyber cab. It is that's it. We're not
we're not announcing anything new.
>> Non-event it is that Elon Musk wasn't
there. Right.
>> Yeah. He he had the people who actually
had product knowledge and if if he's
there it becomes a show about Elon.
>> It was that groundbreaking for the
company. He would have been
>> totally agree.
>> I think they should have messaged that
up front. They should have let us know
instead of me sitting here refreshing
the uh the X feed for Tesla all you know
hoping something would start. They
should have just told us no this is not
a live stream event. This is not a big
this is what we're calling a launch and
the launch is going to include a
15-minute presentation and then we're
going to let influencers write around
and then the next day we're going to let
the general public write around and
that's it. Don't don't ex don't get your
hopes up for a a robot. This is this is
not what this is not what we're
launching. We're launching a cyber cab
and it's cool and it's it's what we
talked about two years ago and it's
actually real and you're actually going
to be able to get in one that drives you
around without without any assistance.
>> Tesla did make a cyber cab with a
steering wheel. That's the only uh Tesla
I would buy.
>> Tesla and Lululemon are down almost the
exact same dollar amount today.
>> Wait, what? Tesla and Lululemon are down
almost the exact same dollar amount
today. About $22 each.
>> That is that is an odd stat.
>> Smoke, bro.
>> It just on my screen. I just did it
right next to each other. Right.
>> Lululemon is the next Nike. Uh
>> dude, I'm telling you right now, this
guy Bur is out of his freaking mind.
He's
>> He's the one He's like short Nebius and
he's long Lulu. Talk about a terrible
portfolio. Oh my god,
>> dude. I I hate to say it, but first of
all, I I've always said I do respect the
fact that he puts his opinions out,
right,
>> ahead of time and allows
>> he has to, right? I mean, it's going to
get disclosed anyways, right? People are
going to figure it out.
>> I guess, man, this is this is
catastrophic. I spent some time on Lulu
this week trying to figure out what he
was seeing in Lulu. I pulled every piece
of data I could pull on Lulu thinking if
hey, you know, if they were going to
beat earnings, this stock could
skyrocket this week. I was desperately
looking for ways that Lulu could
potentially beat earnings. And so
>> I've also been trying to figure it out
because Lulu was I mean it was an
attractive price. I mean it's what like
a 11p or something. I mean I was like
come on
>> it's just it's just not there. It's not
there. Aloe and all these and Bory and
all these guys are just eating into
them.
>> I don't want to hear one thing ever
again about how smart Bur is because I
am telling you there is absolutely no
data that pointed to them having a great
quarter. And so he is just something's
going on with him where
>> he just doesn't I don't know he's
getting in his head. He's coming up with
madeup thesis and madeup things to
support whatever the hell is in his
head.
>> Well, I think he's just he's looking for
some sort of like it looks like
reversion trades, right? Um but what I
think he's missing is that this isn't
the dot bubble, right? Um, and I I feel
like he thinks that there's too much of
a too much of a corlary. And
>> dude, Jordan, none of us should even be
talking about him.
>> Or or if you just completely make the
most insane claims and bets, eventually
you're going to get one right. It's like
sitting at a roulette wheel and putting
putting money on a single number.
Eventually, you're going to get it to
hit.
>> He's completely disconnected. Bur's
completely disconnected from cultural
and social norms, man. Completely
disconnected. And it's it's he has no
clue how people think and behave. He
>> Have you seen how much money he's making
on his newsletter?
>> He's only making a few million a year,
actually. Uh it's not what people think.
He's not making that much money. I mean,
it's a lot of money, don't get me wrong,
but it's not like a hundred million a
year. This guy's too disconnected. He he
no one should be listening to him for
every for anything at this point. And
it's astonishing.
He's he's be we need like he's becoming
the new Kramer. He's literally like he
wanted to become
>> the inverse Bur index will beat the S&P
this year 100%. Like there's there's no
doubt about it.
>> The ticker is just buried. [laughter]
>> The Barry Bur
>> buried. I don't know
>> guys. This stock market has never been
dumber. Institutions, retail traders,
people are so lazy. They're so dopamine.
>> I I can't tell you how many times I read
that XYZ CEO or whatever is buying a
bunch of Nike stock. And I'm like, it is
not time,
>> dude.
Like Tim Cook was apparently out buying
Nike. I'm like, why?
If you're an investor right now and
willing to even do a little bit of
actual work to get to ground truth,
you're going to be a winner, man. Long
term, you'll be a winner because your
competition is horrible in 2026.
Horrible. Uh [laughter] I mean just just
the AI trade alone like the the the
number of people who are investors again
institutionally on Wall Street and in
retail who just will not take the time
to realize that AI is a real thing and
how meaningful it is. That alone that's
the biggest ARB trade in history. the
we're we're going through the biggest
thing that's ever happened to humankind
and most people who are trading the
market just refuse to see it. Like
>> they're like, "Oh, I know. Let's go buy
some Lululemon." [laughter]
>> Jordan's nuts.
>> Final takes on Tesla because I do I I've
seen you on so many other podcasts,
Chris, and you have another big play
that you've been talking about and
people are asking about it here in the
chat. I need to ask you about GTA 6. Oh,
no, no, no. We got to do Optimus first.
Real quick, real quick.
>> Because again, this is another
misunderstanding because that guy,
what's his name? Jason, is it Jason
Calakut from uh
>> what's his name from the All-In Pod who
talked about Optimus? He saw some vid.
He thinks he saw some video.
>> I mean, dude,
>> he's seen he said on numerous occasions
he has seen Optimus 3 and he says it
does amazing things and he can't tell
you what they are. This is so
embarrassing for a guy that's actually
spent a tremendous amount of time deep
diving into all the world's robotics
companies the last three years and
actually understanding what's real and
not real, what matters and what doesn't
matter. Um, and is like not falling for
the tricks of any of these companies. He
makes a statement like that and he's
he's just like he's a normie. He's a
normie walking into a space he knows
nothing about. Talking about a video
that he thinks he saw, not understanding
what any of the KPIs are, what actually
matters. How much time has he actually
spent, if any, talking to and engaging
with roboticists, actual roboticists
that are working on these robots? People
that have come from Optimus that have
like come from out of these companies
that will tell you what the real
problems are they're trying to solve and
you know what the winning company or the
winning hardware platform is actually
going to look like. He he this is the
problem. The problem is we have people
that are going for attention. It's an
attention economy. He's no different. He
wants to hype something because he knows
if he says something about Optimus
that's spectacular that he's going to
get a lot of clicks and views of
himself. And I don't know the guy. He
might be the nicest, greatest guy in the
world. But it bothers me when people
talk about things they know nothing
about. And then investors get all
excited and make decisions based on what
they heard this guy say because they
think he saw something. Every piece of
intelligence that I've been able to
gather tells me, and I've been saying
this for a year and a half, and people
didn't believe me at first, the OP that
the Optimus program is nowhere near
where it needs to be. Uh, in many ways,
has been kind of in shambles. They've
lost a lot of their head talent, as we
all know. Everyone was expecting Optimus
3 to come out in March, April. I said
that's not never going to happen. I said
that back in October of last year, like
six months earlier. I said they're not
doing anything in March or April of next
year with Optimus 3. That's not going to
happen. Now, where are we? We're in
what? September of 26.
No Optimus 3, right? No reveal. Nothing
on the books to even talk about
revealing it. I'm still hearing stuff
about a lot of kind of arguments that
are happening uh with the Hand program.
If you look at the leadership inside of
Tesla, we're I I don't I cannot identify
any bleeding edge leadership in
generalized robotics humanoids. The team
doesn't seem exceptionally
talented to me from what I've heard
about and what I can see. I mean,
there's a handful of companies that are
splitting all the top talent and they're
all having issues kind of getting to the
KPIs they need to get at as quickly as
they wanted to get there. I still am
rooting for Tesla. I still want Optimist
to be massively huge because if they
are, it's going to be one of the
greatest trades on earth. Like I want
Optimus to be a massive success. Not
even for the money, for humanity. Okay?
Like nobody wants Optimus to be a winner
more than I do. So like trust me guys,
the second that I start to hear good
things about Optimus, one, I'm probably
throwing an insane amount of money
levered into Tesla. Two, I will be
genuinely happy for humanity because we
need Optimus to be successful because
they are going to be one of three or
four or five companies that are truly
capable of throwing resources and money
to scale robots around the world to help
humans, right? To help our civilization,
to help our economy, all the things to
help the elderly, to help people in
need. Like I want Optimist to win, but
it's not winning right now, guys. I hate
to break it to you. It's not winning.
Okay? Like there's nothing spectacular
that I'm aware of, and I know a lot of
people in the space that's happening at
Optimus right now, unless I'm missing
something. So, if you're investing
aggressively in Tesla right now because
of Optimus, just do your homework. Make
sure it's more than just a random guy
from the all-in pod saying he saw a
video and they're 18 months ahead of
everyone else when I happen to know that
he doesn't even know about everyone else
because I know of companies that he
hasn't done his research on. So, how can
he make that assessment when he hasn't
gone in deep with everyone else in the
space, right? Yeah. Anyway, that that's
my rant. I'm done on that. That's it. I
mean that that's a legitimate rant and a
legitimate point that you have and I I
you know I'm hoping and betting like you
that that Tesla will be able to pull it
off, but it's it's not a done deal and
it's not a sure thing and there is
always there's always a possibility that
they'll fail. But I think that they have
a better chance than and I'm not saying
that they're going to be the only robot
that survives, but they have a better
chance than many of the robot humanoid
robotic players. And so as a part of a
portfolio that wants to be involved in
humanoid robots, it is in my basket.
>> I'd rather wait. I'd rather wait only
because I have a lot of good intel and
I'll probably know when they're getting
close and I'll throw my money in then
because money is precious right now and
I don't want money sitting in a company
for two months or six months when I
could be putting it to work getting
massive returns on other trades. Like
the cost of capital right now is really
high. Uh the AI trade is on and I every
dollar matters. I I I I need to put my
dollars to work now. I can't sit around
waiting for Tesla to finally hit it out
of the park with Optimus. When I think
they're about to do that, I'll shift
some money over to Tesla.
So, that that's that.
>> Now, can we talk about GTA 6?
>> Yeah. And now you're going to really see
me get frustrated
>> because this
[laughter]
I've seen you all over the internet
talking about GTA 6. I need to know the
latest based on you you've seen you've
seen the the footage. You've seen the
stuff on Netflix. You've seen you you've
actually seen something now. And this is
this is what you were waiting for
before. Where are we with the take two
trade?
>> Well, I've learn I've learned a lot.
I've grown as a person and as investor
over the past week and a half would take
two.
>> I I love that you're able to admit that
that you're that you're you're not
already at the top level you can
possibly be as an investor that you you
have room to improve.
>> Oh, massive massive room to improve
always. Uh because you know why, Dave?
Because the market is always shifting
and changing and and the players in it
are shifting and you have to play along
with the game, right? The game is always
changing. So as the game changes, I have
to change with it. I had this thesis on
take two that the depth of interest in
the game itself, the quality of the game
itself, and the excitement around the
game itself would ultimately drive the
units that they're able to push, but
more importantly would ultimately drive
the ARPO, the the a average revenue uh
basically per per player in the game
once they release the uh live version,
the online version of the game and
that's all that matters for Take 2. So,
I was laser focused on the success or
failure of this game game uh play
trailer that they released right now.
This game people have been waiting for
13 years to see this right and so the
expectations were so high in the my
benchmark was that it was going to be a
disappointment. Clearly benchmark was
that it' be a disappointment. They came
out with the trailer and it definitely
was not a disappointment. I I mean, I
read probably and I'm I'm not messing
with you guys right now. I read well
over 10,000 comments. Well over 10,000
comments over the 72 hours after that
video came out because I want to get
through all of the BS investor comments.
I just want to get to the meat of actual
gamers and how they really felt. And of
course, there's a subsection of gamers
that no matter what happened, they were
so pissed off that the game is digital
and not coming out on a disc that they
were going to rip Rockstar no matter
what. There's some gamers that are like,
"It's just a better version of GTA." Of
course it is. It's GTA, dude. What are
you expecting a different game? Like, of
course, it's a just a better version of
GTA. But I will say this,
90% 90% of what I read was astonishingly
positive. Like super excited. Like
cannot count the days until this game
actually comes out and they could start
playing it. So my thesis on the ground
truth is that we are more likely than
not based on the 27 minutes of gameplay
to have a highly engaged base of GTA 6
players when the game comes out that the
company could then build on and deliver
higher than expected uh unit sales
because the unit sales estimates in the
first quarter uh that the game is out to
few months range from 30 million to 50
million. So my assumption now is that
they will be at the higher end of that
range. And my assumption is that the
engagement level with the game will be
high enough that hope that an educated
investor community could then connect
the dots to them having a very high
arpoo once the online version of the
game comes out which would enable a
company like take 2 to generate two to3
billion dollars a year from
microtransactions for years.
>> What have we seen about the in-game
revenue opportunities? Have we seen
anything indicating that that timeline
is within the first year of release? Are
we or are we just looking at game
downloads in year one and in-game
revenue in year two or three? Okay,
Dave, the biggest takeaway is that
investors far and wide are so lazy that
no one actually is even taking the time
to understand what the benchmark is that
GTA 6 needs to beat or miss for this to
be a success or failure for for Take 2.
And as someone who's been trading GTA
releases since 1999,
I was trading Take 2 in 1999. Yes, I'm
that old. Uh this people are like, "You
don't know what you're doing. You're in
late." Dude, I've been doing this for 27
years with Take Two. Okay. Uh back in 99
investors were smart as hell. Like
everybody knew the benchmarks. We were
doing deep analysis on the numbers and
and so that's where my brain still is.
But in 2026, it's all vibes. Every time
someone comes out and says, "You're
crazy to invest in Take 2." It's baked
into the price. What's baked in? 30
million, 40 million units, 50 million,
70 million. They can't answer because
they haven't even taken the time to look
at that. What are poos baked in? 30
bucks a year, 40, 80, 60. They don't
even know what that they don't even know
what that number means. So like
investors are so dumb, but but it's the
reality. You can complain about it, but
this is the reality. So, how do you win
on a trade when no one even understands
the benchmarks that you think the
company's going to beat? So, even if
they beat those benchmarks, if investors
don't even know that they beat these
madeup benchmarks, then how do you win?
It's very difficult, Dave. Very freaking
difficult. And what you just said about
the online version of the game, the
rumor, a rumor comes out that they're
going to delay it two years. Completely
unsubstantiated rumor. Maybe it's right.
I doubt it. But if they are going to
delay it two years, it's because the
company sees a reason to do so. Meaning,
they think it's actually going to work
in their benefit for some reason. I
don't know why they would. That seems
insane to me. The last GTA in 2013,
they released the online version of the
game like within two to three weeks of
releasing the like the story mode of the
game.
>> Yeah. So, it's hard for me to believe
that Take 2 thinks the move here is to
delay it two years because so much of
what GTA is is microtransactions.
GTA is the game that proved that
microtransactions can work on a triple
Aless console game and generate billions
of dollars of revenue. They are one of
the innovators in this space and they've
had over a decade to figure out that
model and if you look at what they're
doing with microtransactions on this
game in terms of the number of things
that you could theoretically do in the
game, whether it's the number of things
you can eventually buy that have been
rumored and they've come out with, it's
going to be spectacular. But all that
hinges on one thing, the gameplay has to
be fun as hell. And we don't know yet.
All we have is 27 minutes. But based on
the 27 minutes, it you have to make the
assessment that yes, it's more likely to
be a killer game experience that than a
dud. All right. Now, people are like,
"Oh, but but the narrative is not the
story is not they didn't even release
the story, dude. What the hell are you
talking about, dude? It was a 27minute
in-game play. They did not want to give
the story out, dude. How are you
complaining that the story doesn't have
a good enough narrative when they
haven't even told you yet? That's so and
there's so many people that just want to
rip on everything in life. They're
[\h__\h] miserable, dude. Like, it's
pisses me off. Anyway, the bottom line
is here's my trade because everyone
wants to know my trade. Uh I think you
guys know this. I might have shared this
with you guys, but uh the Thursday
before the basically the Thursday when
this thing came out or whatever right
before it came out uh or no the day came
out uh Take Two dropped a lot. It was
down like five bucks and then the
trailer came out. I went all in. Okay. I
bought massive options on Take Two, one
day options. They expired on Friday. I
sold them the next day. Made a few
hundred,000 on that trade. Now, I didn't
sell all of them. I actually let a lot
of them roll into the weekend and
exercise, and it gave me a massive long
equity position in take two. Then this
person shorted $700,000 of puts on take
two on the open on Monday. All right.
Then there was a BFA report that, by the
way, reiterated a $367
target price for take two, which is like
a 70% increase. But everybody took one
line out of this report which was like
we don't think the game play or or GTA
is going to like move the excitement
needle for units or something like I
don't know some random line but yet they
still had a price target 70% higher but
everybody caught that one negative line
it went viral. So, you had this guy
shorting it, which freaked everyone out
in the morning with puts. Who who knows
what? Who knows what, right? You have
this one random line from a BFA thing.
You have a rumor that basically says
that the online getting delayed to what?
>> You get delay rumors is the biggest
thing.
>> Well, no, you have a delay rumor on the
online,
>> but then but then people started
interpolating that into delays on the
actual game, which isn't even a thing.
Like just they're so locked in for this
November release date. Like it doesn't
make sense,
>> guys. We had stupidity on top of
stupidity on top of stupidity on top of
stupidity. And do you know what I took
from this guys? That's the world we live
in. So as an investor, don't fight it.
You better don't fight it. That's just
where we are. So I lost more money on my
equity position on Monday than I made on
that options position the Friday before.
I lo I ended up being down in total a
few hundred thousand which again for me
not the end of the world. We all know
that right now knowing what I know now
>> I doubled my position on that day by the
way.
>> On which day? Monday.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Probably smart. So like I did
lower my position some. And here's why.
At the same exact time Amazon got
ripped. Why? Because of stupidity on top
of stupidity. They have a lawsuit coming
out of North Carolina that's going to go
on for years that no one's going to be
talking about. starting next week. Okay.
Then they have interest rates going up
the next day, which historically is bad
for companies like Amazon. But when
they're increasing their, you know,
their their profits by 40%, I mean, who
the hell cares about a half point
interest rate move, okay? So, it goes
down another five bucks. So, I need to
find money in my portfolio to go in
deeper on Amazon. We all know what I do
when it comes to Amazon. So, I took some
money out of take two even though I got
hit because if I'm going to go in
deeper, it's going to be Amazon, not
take two. I have a really nice long
position in take two and I might
increase it, but it was this weekend the
number two largest position. Now, it got
knocked down to like number five in my
portfolio. I
still think all the things that I
thought when that trailer came out are
true, but I do not know the timeline for
the investor base to come to terms with
that ground truth that I believe is
true. And also, there's still a massive
amount of risk with the game play not
being as good as it is in the trailer
because we've only seen 27 minutes.
Maybe the narrative is terrible. Maybe
when the game actually comes out, the
fact that it's so intense with all the
things you have to do to stay alive and
to like they made it more complex, maybe
people don't like that. There's still a
lot of risk, guys, in the GTA release,
but I'm still more more positive
meaningfully than negative going into
the November release. Also, and this is
really important, okay?
Could I have never been part of a moment
in time where we didn't need as guys
specifically the male loneliness ep
epidemic is real. Okay. We needed a
cultural moment to connect. Okay. Uh a
crossgenerational moment where guys in
their 40s and 50s can like actually all
be doing the same thing at the same
time. Same thing with guys in their 30s
and 20s. Okay. I think this is the most
crossgenerational
game that we've ever had. I think it's
needed right now. We used to all watch
TV on Thursday nights together. No one
does that crap anymore. We all listen to
different music. There's no sense of
connectivity except when everyone's
waiting 5 hours for the same hyped fro
yo in Manhattan or or sweatshirt or
skincare in LA, right? So, like we're
dying to all be connected about
something and guys don't really have any
of those opportunities. This is it. This
is the moment for every guy globally to
feel connected. This is our thing that
we can do. And come November 17th, is
it? or 19th,
half the guys in the world pretty much
are all going to be doing the same
thing, talking about the same thing,
chatting about it, doing it with your
buddies, like even though it's not
online, you're all doing on your own.
Like, it's just it's going to be a
moment, man. And I think we need it. And
I actually think just like the Olympics
was this summer, GTA is going to be a
wildly positive thing that is you're
going to hear about. And if you're not
doing it, you're gonna be like, I need
to do this because everyone I know is
doing it, right? Or like this is so
because you know how many how hard
>> Yes and no. I mean, I get your point and
I think it will be a cultural moment. I
have zero interest in picking up video
games for the first time because there's
a cultural moment going around.
>> I said half much like I'm not going to
um go
>> GTA 6 there are a ton of people that
play video games that are that are
pumped about this.
>> Yeah. No, I get it. I get it. I know
that it's going to be a a big deal. It
it will affect me in zero way at all.
>> The biggest deal, not a big deal, the
biggest deal. I think
>> I I think a bigger deal will be, you
know, the cultural moment of getting my
foldable iPhone with a bunch of other
dudes who think that that's cool.
>> I just
>> a different a different a different
version of nerd. That's all.
>> Folds and like just more stuff to break.
That's that's a no, dog. Dave, I was
excited about the foldable phone, but
then the more I researched it, it became
less and less exciting. Like, they're
making so many like sacrifices for it.
It's not going to be what I thought it
was. Maybe I'm wrong, but I don't know,
man. I don't think I want it. I'm just
going to get the new regular Pro iPhone.
>> I will probably get the new regular Pro,
too. Mainly because uh it it's missing
the zoom camera, the the the longest
lens.
Exactly. And that's important. Like I
got to tape,
>> dude. Yesterday I was taping my son's
football game from like up in the
stands.
>> So there there is a new feature in iOS
27 though that will allow you to have
two phones share the same number and
they'll be able to hand off between each
other. So that will allow you to have
both the fold that you take with you on
an airplane to watch, you know, a movie
and have more screen real estate when
you need it. And then you'll have the
pro when you need to do a pro-like
activity like filming a, you know,
football game. C
>> can I say one more thing about GTA? It's
pretty important. You know, these this
pre-sale data that everyone was this is
like the the fifth level of stupidity
that people added over the week. They
only pre-sold like less than 5 million
and people were comparing that to the 7
million that they pre-sold in 2013.
Well, first of all, it's a digital game.
There's no reason to pre purchase a
digital game, guys. Are you giving them
your money now and you'll be able to
download it on the day? [snorts]
>> Second. Second, there's still like two
plus months before the game comes out.
So, there's still an insane amount of
time for those pre-sales to go way up.
Not that it even freaking matters
because it's a digital game. But three,
the company that created all of this
spectacle about pre-sales that people
are like they're too low is called
Sensor Tower. And they are best well
known for predicting within a pretty
tight degree of margin Steam games where
they have numerous data points that
they've been able to refine over the
years and they could predict pre-sales
within like 3 to 5%. Well, guess what
they just started doing for the first
time this summer? Probably because of
GTA. They want to get hype and marketing
exposure. They now have an algorithm
that they are going to attempt to
predict pre-sales on console games,
right? They've never even done this
before. We have no history of whether
they are off by 5% or 50%. Because the
methodology hasn't been proven. It
hasn't been tested. It hasn't been
refined. This is not what they generally
do. They generate pre-sales numbers off
of about four to four and a half million
gamers that they have in their like in
their system where they can kind of see
what their wish list has. They look at
rankings. They look at all kinds of
different things, but they've never
really done this in a proven way for
console games. So, we don't even know if
we can trust their data. But even if
they're right, I don't even think it
matters. Again, it's digital and we have
two two and a half months left till this
game comes out.
>> So,
>> again, every single thing that is a rip
against GTA is either false or really
doesn't matter that much. And and so
I'll leave it at that. I have a pretty
decentsized long position in take two.
It's not crazy, but it's pretty decent
still. And I might lever up as I start
to see other things and we get closer to
the release.
>> But I'm honestly, guys,
>> you're in early on take two. You might
get more. You're not in early on Tesla.
You're waiting to see a robot before you
even think about pulling the trigger.
>> Yeah, but I got deeper into Amazon this
week. I did. I got Amazon. I love
Amazon. That's
>> so much. I love it so much. Um I just
love it when it drops. I love it when it
drops like this because it's it's just
such not a sexy company. It's
diversified.
It th this generation of investors if
they can't obviously see how a company
can two to 3x in in the near-term
future, they're just not excited about
it. Amazon's probably not gonna two or
3x anytime soon. But dude, I'm telling
you, man, God, that company is just I
can't own enough of it. I just can't.
And every time it just drops and comes
back, it's just it's just gold for me.
It just makes my whole week cuz I just
start selling other stuff and going
deeper and more levered into Amazon. And
I'm fine. whatever happens the next few
weeks, next couple months, I I still am
at a point where I prefer to see it drop
than go up. Like even though I'm now
starting to lever up in Amazon, I still
prefer to lose that money so that I can
put even more money at lower prices. So
>> you you've got a a really strong mental
ability to do that. I I hate seeing my
stocks go down even though I know I get
to buy more of them at a lower price.
>> Well, so Dave
It's all about conviction. Let's just
let's just say you had a crystal ball.
Let me just ask both of you guys
something. If you had a crystal ball and
had 100% certainty around
>> Let me put on my crystal ball glasses
because I just realized that these are
essentially your glasses.
[clears throat]
>> Yeah, they're not bad. So you if you
want I got a lot of my glasses. I I can
I can give you some.
>> I actually had these before you started
wearing this style. I just I just found
them here at this house and I I use them
as my outdoor glasses.
>> All right. So question. You have a
crystal ball. you know, factually
something's going to happen at some
point in the medium-term future. Would
you have a lot invested in that thing,
but you could theoretically put more in?
And again, it's 100% certainty. Would
you not want that thing to drop, lose
the money so you can go in even deeper
at a lower price because you know for a
fact now I'm not saying I know for a
fact that Amazon is going to do XYZ in
the future, but my conviction has never
been higher on a company of of this
size. It's just a timeline issue and and
a macro issue, right? Macro could take
it down certainly. Uh there's always an
anomaly that could happen at the company
that could take it down. There's unknown
unknowns that I don't even can't even
think of. But for the most part, I just
I just want to put more money in Amazon.
And I know this is this is how I know. I
was I was thinking about this yesterday
watching my son play football and I was
thinking about Amazon because I'm
thinking about Amazon every day. And I
was thinking, I know at some point in
the future, I'm gonna look back at
September of 2026
and wish I went deeper into Amazon.
That's I can't stop thinking about it.
I'm going to be like, as deep as I am,
even though I'm levered now, again, I'm
not levered enough. I'm not deep enough.
I should be putting more dollars into
Amazon. This is a good time for my
>> Your hypothetical situation is flawed
though because if I had a crystal ball,
I would and I knew for certainty in my
crystal ball that this was 100%
certainty in the future. I just want it
to go down. No, I would I would use the
crystal ball to find the bottom, find
the lowest price, and then just buy it
there. Like
>> your crystal ball has nothing to do with
stock price to company performance.
>> Company performance, Dave, not stock
price. So you don't know how the market
is going to react, when they're going to
react, but you know that this company is
going to knock it out of the park over
and over. That part, you know, 100%.
>> Only a partial crystal ball that can
only tell a part of the future. Yeah, I
totally would want it to go down more.
Yeah, I in that scenario. Yes.
>> So, let's remind everyone, we're not
financial adviserss. Uh we're talking
about what we're doing. My risk
tolerance in my account, I can guarantee
you, is probably wildly different than
anyone watching this show.
>> Although, I did see a good comment.
>> This uh this person says that they trade
on vibes and Chris's advice.
>> No, don't do that, man.
>> When we were talking about how today's
traders are stupid because of vibe
trading, well, there you go.
>> Unless we're all dumb money together
>> unless it's in a vibe specific account.
Vibe account
>> that is you literally don't care about
it. Do not do that, guys. Don't.
>> I I have a Vibe account. I will I will I
will put $1,000 into random options just
because I saw someone tweet something
that I thought, "Oh, yeah. I I could see
that happening." And I And I lose I lose
like eight out of 10 of those for sure.
>> That's my vibe trade for you right
there. All right, I have a a limited
capacity for vibe trading and yeah, it
occasionally works.
>> There's one more thing we have to talk
about before we go and it's Robin Hood.
Did you see Vlad's tweet last night to
the AMCO?
>> Oh, no. I saw his tweet. Yes. To uh
someone about tokenizing
uh it was a is the AMC CEO saying that
you can you cannot possibly tokenize AMC
stock because that's illegal. And
>> and what did tweet?
>> His tweet was like, "What's what's the
problem here?"
>> Like, "What are you worried about?"
Yeah. What are you worried? Dude, let me
just tell you something. Vla at Robin
Hood is an animal. And that's why I'm
invested in Robin Hood. Okay? I'm
invested in Robin Hood for that exact
tweet that he put out last night. And I
also said this, like, I've never been a
crypto bro, but I've always related to
all those guys. And like Robin Hood is
the thing we have in common. It's that
intersection. And like I'm riding with
the crypto bros on this one. And it's
fun because like I I relate to the guys.
I don't relate to crypto specifically,
but the fact that crypto's running and
Robin Hood's running, like I love it
when we're all running together, man,
it's so fun because there's nothing that
beats a crypto bro during a bull crypto
market, man. you just want to hang with
like I have a few of these friends
>> and man it is fun times when crypto is
hopping dude like I'm get I'm getting
crypto memes from some of these guys
every day and I just know they are
flying these guys are psychotic by the
way like I still I don't get them really
but I love the energy dude I love it and
by the way this is why I love Robin Hood
because I told you the second that
crypto turns around I'm going even
deeper into Robin Hood okay cuz Robin
Hood wins without crypto, but with
crypto, Robin Hood slaughters slaughters
with crypto. So, what are they doing?
They're com they're tokenizing these
companies,
>> tokenizing assets, including company
stock and not for uh sale in the US, but
for other markets to let people in other
countries invest in the US stock market.
The same thing that I would like to see
them do for foreign stocks that we don't
have easy access to, just tokenize it. I
don't care if I own the actual stock or
a token of the stock.
>> Yeah. But how does that work though? I
mean, does it does it tied directly or
does it just kind of does it?
>> Yeah. No, they they would one to one
they would buy the stock, tokenize it,
and have the actual underlying asset.
>> There are assets under
>> in custody. Yeah.
>> Under the tokens, right?
>> Yep.
>> Yeah. Then what's what's wrong? It seems
fine.
>> It's that's what that's what Vlad said
basically. What's your problem, D?
What's your problem?
>> What's your concern? [laughter]
>> We had a we had a monkey uh tweet that
to us. [gasps]
A and um so listen, Vlad said on ice
coffee hour recently that he they were
going to do it for foreign stocks that
it's especially because there was a lot
of demand for Korean stocks that none of
us can invest in. So it sounds like it's
on the plate of things that they're
working on. There are some regulatory
issues
>> market, right? I mean, don't you want to
just market your stocks? That seems like
another way to just market the stocks. I
mean, am I crazy?
>> What's the problem? What's the problem?
>> There's no problem.
>> There is no problem.
>> Oh, I love Robin Hood, man. I love I
love that company, dude. And um yeah, we
we'll see we'll see what happens going
forward. I don't know what's going to go
on with all this crypto stuff, but hey,
as long as crypto is running, Robin Hood
should be in a good place.
>> Yep.
>> So, all right. Anything else, guys? This
has been a
>> this I mean we've already gone over our
aotted time here today. Uh we thank all
we we got a pretty goodized audience.
>> Yeah, we miss you guys. And by the way,
I I do I do have Listen, I it's awesome
that the retail market is blowing up,
man. and and people want like people are
inviting me to be on their shows which
is cool because it brings new people
into the social arb investing world
which I think is like really important
just generally. Uh so I'm going to keep
on doing those shows. You know Dave,
they invited me to come speak uh at
Columbia Business School. I'm going up
in a couple weeks.
>> I'm bringing a camera guy to tape to
tape that too. And um yeah, we'll we'll
continue to do our stuff but we will get
our show on more regular. We felt bad
about this. Dave, the problem is Dave is
in Mexico.
>> You can't blame it on me. I have very
solid internet. I have a a podcasting
microphone.
>> Like, you can't blame this on me. I I
blame this on your on your schedule and
you're appearing on nine other podcasts
between our last episode and today.
[laughter]
>> Somehow you have time for all of them,
but not for us.
>> It's a little bit. Jordan, what have you
been up to lately? Like personally, like
what have you been doing?
>> What
>> What have you been doing personally?
like the last Have you What do you just
What have you been doing?
>> I don't know. Hanging out. Uh, we went
to New York um for a friend's birthday.
Uh, that was fun.
>> Oh, that's cool. Are are you Is this
going to be an A&M's year or no?
>> Football. Are you talking football right
now, dude?
>> Has an uncanny ability to just have a
great team and go like eight and four.
So, yeah, I'm looking forward to getting
my heart broken. That's what I'm looking
forward to.
>> Hey. Hey, join the team, man. SMU join
>> SMU did the same thing last year to you
guys. I know.
>> Yeah, I am emotionally prepared to get
destroyed again this year.
>> College football is designed to break
your heart, right? Unless you with that
many teams,
um, you know, it's just it's pure luck.
A lot of times
>> it hardens you. That is for sure. Dave,
are you coming home soon? The weather's
starting to cool down. It started
yesterday.
>> I saw you having multiple days under
100, but then it goes right back to 100.
I'm going to be there as soon as there
are one week under a hundred. I'll be
back. No, I'm I'm thinking October.
>> Oh my god.
>> What are we September 4th right now?
I'll be there by October 1st, if not
sooner.
>> Um, by the way, guys, no peptide trade
right now. We thought about it. The
peptide market shifted. We're going to
do an episode. I'm looking at the
questions here. Oh, yeah.
>> I put them on the screen.
>> Yeah,
>> Tim has gone nowhere since we started
talking about this. Um,
>> yeah, there's a reason we didn't do the
peptide episode. Trust me, lots of
research went into it and I just didn't
have anything meaningful to talk about
after that research. So, like it just
the episode didn't come together like we
would have hoped, but there was a reason
for it. We don't want to do an episode
just to talk about something when
there's nothing when there's too many
like unknowns. We just we just didn't
feel like it was needed. Um
>> although e I think that even when we
don't have a strong conviction trade to
talk about or I I think we should get
back on the schedule and Friday might be
the day to do it. Remember when we had
our Friday happy hour shows where we
came with nothing with no with no agenda
with no talking points and we just get
on and and take take questions.
>> Yeah.
>> I think we should get back to trying to
do that once a week even weeks we don't
have actual content.
>> I like it
>> because I know that people like that.
No, let's do it. Let's do it. All right.
Have a wonderful Is it Labor Day, right?
Labor Day weekend.
>> Uh, yes, that is the That is the
upcoming holiday.
>> It's a It's a three-day.
>> All right, guys.
>> All right. Thanks so much for watching.
We're Dumb Money. We'll see you next
time.
[music]